Here are some questions I thought of that I'm interested in.
Pensei em algumas perguntas nas quais estou interessado.
First, how has employment in the US varied over time?
Primeiro, como foi a variação de empregos nos EUA com o tempo?
Of course, you could ask the same question about another country.
É claro que você pode fazer a mesma pergunta sobre outro país.
I'm particularly interested in the US, because that's where I live.
Eu estou particularmente interessado nos EUA porque é onde moro.
But you may have another country you're interested in investigating.
Mas você pode estar interessado em investigar outro país.
In the most recent year we have data on, what are the highest and
No ano mais recente sobre o qual temos dados, quais são os maiores e
lowest employment levels out of all the countries?
menores níveis de emprego de todos os demais países?
Which countries have those employment levels?
Quais países têm esses níveis de emprego?
And where is the US on that spectrum?
Onde se encontra os EUA nesse espectro?
Of course, I could ask these same questions for
É claro que eu também posso fazer as mesmas perguntas para
any of the other variables in the data set, as well.
qualquer outra variável do conjunto de dados.
I'm also interested in whether there are any consistent trends across countries.
Também estou interessado em saber se há alguma tendência consistente entre os países.
For example, have there been any global recessions and
Por exemplo, houve alguma recessão mundial e,
if so, can I find them in this data?
em caso afirmativo, ela se encontra nestes dados?
Answering this last question would be a bit complicated and we're not going
Pode ser complicado responder a essa última pergunta. Não veremos isso
to get into it in this lesson, but we can definitely tackle the others.
nesta lição, mas podemos ver as demais.